Hey!
!هنا
Good morning!
!صباح الخير
If I can be like the idol, Miki-chan,
،لو أستطيع أن أكون مثل الآيدول ميكي-تشان
and be just as cool and successful
وأكون رائعة وناجحة
when I
عندما
start at my new school...
...أبدأ في مدرستي الجديدة
I can make lots...
...أستطيع تشكيل الكثير
and lots...
...والكثير
of friends!
!من الأصدقاء
Yes!
!مرحى
I did it!
!فعلتُها
Wow, this water's cold.
هذا الماء بارد
I wondered who I just saw fall down there.
تساءلتُ من الّذي سقط هناك للتو
Hi, Taira-san!
!مرحباً يا تايرا-سان
Should've known it was you, Komichi.
كان ينبغي أن أعلم بأنّها أنتِ يا كوميتشي
Oh, I was just, uh...
...كنتُ فقط
practicing swimming while fully clothed.
أتمرّن على السّباحة بملابسي الكاملة
I'll give you a lift home. Hop in the back.
سأوصلكِ إلى المنزل. اصعدي للخلف
I hear you got into the middle school you tested for.
سمعتُ أنّكِ قُبِلتِ في المدرسة الإعداديّة التي خضعتِ لاختبار فيها
Yeah, Roubai Academy.
أجل، أكاديميّة روباي
It's a private school!
!إنّها مدرسة خاصّة
I heard it's a tough school. Didn't your mother go there?
سمعتُ أنّها مدرسة مُتشدّدة. ألم تذهب أمّكِ إليها؟
Yeah. That's why I'm so happy I got in!
!أجل. لهذا أنا سعيدة لأنّني التحقتُ بها
Are you, now?
هل أنتِ كذلك الآن؟
They say each class has more than ten students in it!
!يُقال بأنّ في كلّ صفّ يوجد أكثر من عشرة تلاميذ
I can't even imagine it!
!لا أستطيع حتّى تخيّل ذلك
Well, you were always the only kid in your class
بالطبع، فقد كنتِ دوماً وحيدة في صفّكِ
back at Futaba Elementary.
في ابتدائيّة فوتابا
Good for you!
!أنا مسرور لأجلكِ
Yeah!
!أجل
Akebi's Sailor Uniform
زيّ البحّارة الرسميّ الخاص بأكيبي
Thank you!
!شكراً لك
Episode One The Sailor Uniform I Always Wanted
الحلقة الأولى زيّ البحّارة الرسميّ الّذي لطالما أردتُه
I-I'm home.
عـ-عدت
Mom, Onee-chan's home!
!أمّي، عادت أونيه-تشان
Her footsteps sound a bit fishy, don't they?
تبدو خطوات أقدامها مُريبة قليلاً، أليس كذلك؟
I'll go look!
!سأذهب وألقي نظرة
You're such a tomboy!
!تتشبّهين بالصّبيان
Who did you take after, anyway?
من تقلّدين على أيّ حال؟
Oh, right.
بالمناسبة
Your dad sent a message to congratulate you.
أرسل والدكِ رسالة لتهنئتكِ
Really?
حقّاً؟
Great work! Congratulations!
!أحسنت صنعاً !تهانيّي
But if you fall asleep at your desk, you'll catch a cold.
،لكن إذا نمتِ على مقعدكِ .سوف تبردين
Huh?
ماذا؟
How does Dad know about that? He didn't see me.
كيف علمَ أبي بهذا؟ لم يرني
Try scrolling up.
اصعدي بالشّاشة للأعلى
Saved them all Nice!
حفظتُها كلّها !جميل
Read
مقروءة
Saved them all Nice!
حفظتُها كلّها !جميل
Read
مقروءة
Saved them all Nice!
حفظتُها كلّها !جميل
Saved them all Nice!
!ماذا؟
What?!
مقروءة
My parents are taking sneak shots of their daughter!
يلتقط والدايّ صوراً لابنتهما خِلسة
Yay!
!مرحى
I can't trust anyone anymore...
...لا أستطيع الوثوق بأحد بعد الآن
Hi, Dad?
مرحباً، أبي؟
Yeah. How was work?
أجل. كيف حال العمل؟
Maybe so, but I wasn't sleeping the whole time!
!ربّما ذلك، لكن لم أكن نائمة طوال الوقت
That's your complaint?
أهذه شكواك؟
I was studying!
!كنتُ أدرس
You'd better save some cuter pictures of me next time.
من الأفضل أن تحفظ صوراً أظرف لي في المرّة المقبلة
I just thought of something...
...فكّرتُ في شيء للتو
but it's a secret for now.
لكنّه سرّ حاليّاً
Uh-huh.
نعم
Okay. Got it.
حسناً. فهمت
Talk to you later, then.
أتكلّم معك لاحقاً إذاً
What'd he say?
ماذا قال؟
That he'll do his best at work, so he can be home by next month.
بأنّه سيبذل قصارى جهده في العمل، وذلك كي يعود إلى المنزل في الشّهر المقبل
Yay!
!مرحى
Well, then, ready for the thing you've been waiting for?
حسناً إذاً، هل أنتِ جاهزة للشيء الذي كنتِ تنتظرينه؟
Yay! Yay!
!مرحى! مرحى
Yeah.
أجل
I chose Roubai Academy because I've always wanted to wear a sailor uniform!
اخترتُ أكاديميّة روباي لأنّني لطالما !أردتُ ارتداء زيّ بحّارة رسميّ
I was really nervous at my exam and interview,
،كنتُ متوتّرة جدّاً في امتحاني ومقابلتي
but now I finally get to wear one!
!لكن الآن سأتمكّن أخيراً من ارتداء واحد
I wonder if even someone like me can look good in one.
أتساءل ما إن كان حتّى شخصاً مثلي سيليق به زيّ كهذا
Stand up straight! She can't measure you!
!قِفي جيّداً! لا تستطيع أخذ مقاسكِ
Wh-What do you think?
ما-ما رأيكِ؟
You've gained weight.
زاد وزنكِ
What?!
!ماذا؟
You did spend a lot of time sitting down to study.
قضيتِ وقتاً طويلاً في الجلوس للدراسة
No! No way! I'll drop the weight! I swear!
!لا! مستحيل! سأخفّف الوزن! أقسم
Get changed. It's time to go.
بدّلي ملابسكِ. حان وقت الذهاب
Time to go!
!حان وقت الذهاب
Measure me again later!
!خذي مقاسي مجدّداً لاحقاً
I mean, you're going to all the trouble of making it for me.
أعني بأنّكِ ستتكبّدين كلّ عناء صنعه لي
I can't let it go to waste.
لا أريده أن يذهب سُدى
Even in her sleep, all she's been talking about is sailor uniforms.
حتّى في منامها، كلّ ما تتحدّث عنه هو زيّ البحّار
Kao!
!كاو
She was yapping so much, I couldn't sleep.
كانت تثرثر كثيراً لدرجة لم أستطع فيها النّوم
Well, wearing a sailor uniform has always been your dream.
حسناً، لطالما كان ارتداء زيّ بحّارة رسميّ حلمكِ
Yeah!
!أجل
So I really have to do a good job on it.
لذا عليّ أن أبذل جهداً كبيراً عليه حقّاً
What were the kids at Roubai Academy like when you were there?
كيف كان الطلّاب في أكاديميّة روباي عندما كنتِ هناك؟
A lot of them were really interesting.
كان الكثير منهم مثيرين للاهتمام
There were a lot of rich, classy kids, too.
الكثير من الطلّاب الأثرياء الأنيقين
The total opposite of me!
!بعكسي تماماً
Will I even be able to talk to them?
هل سأتمكّن حتّى من التكلّم معهم؟
I went in every day thinking, "Time to flip the hierarchy!"
"!صرتُ أفكّر قائلة، "حان وقت قلب الهرَميّة
Like I was preparing for war.
كما لو كنتُ أستعدّ لحرب
But I'm not as strong as you are, Mom.
لكن لستُ قويّة مثلكِ يا أمّي
Fabrics Store Nihori
متجر نيهوري للأقمشة
Car Rental
تأجير سيّارات
Just be who you are, Komichi.
كوني على طبيعتكِ فحسب يا كوميتشي
All you need is confidence and a smile.
كلّ ما تحتاجينه هو الثّقة والابتسامة
Okay, let's look for some fabric.
حسناً، لنبحث عن بعض الأقمشة
There are so many bolts of fabric!
!هناك الكثير من لفائف الأقمشة
One of these is going to be my...
...واحدة من هذه ستكون
Here it is!
!ها هو
Chambray
شمبري
Denim
دَنيم
Serge/ Gabardine
سيرج/ غبردين
That was quick!
!كان ذلك سريعاً
This is a type of fabric called "serge."
"هذا نوع من الأقمشة يدعى "سيرج
We'll make the sailor collar, skirt, and cuffs from this.
سنصنع ياقة البحّارة والتنّورة وأطراف الكمّ من هذا القماش
This is gonna become my sailor suit!
!ستصبح هذه بدلة البحّارة الخاصّة بي
And this one is called "gabardine."
"ويُدعى هذا قماش "غبردين
We'll use it for the body and sleeves.
سنستخدمه للجسد والأكمام
There are a few different shades of white.
هناك بضع درجات مختلفة من اللّون الأبيض
That's just a matter of preference.
هذه مسألة تفضيلات فحسب
I like the bolder one on the left!
!أحبّ الغامق على اليسار
It's so shimmery and smooth!
!إنّه لمّاع جدّاً وأملس
Isn't fabric shopping fun, Mom?
أليس التسوّق لشراء الأقمشة ممتعاً يا أمّي؟
Whoa...
...بئساً
I think the ribbon should be on the larger side.
أعتقد ينبغي أن تكون الأشرطة أكبر
It'll look cute.
سيبدو ظريفاً
Uh-huh!
!أجل
Onee-chan, do you need help?
أونيه-تشان، هل تحتاجين مساعدة؟
Nah, I'm totally fine.
لا، أنا بخير تماماً
It's the stripes that make a sailor uniform.
الأشرطة هي ما يكوّن زيّ البحّارة الرّسمي
Wait, wait!
!لحظة، لحظة
Mom! I like this one!
!أمّي! أعجبتني هذه
You've been humming all day.
كنتِ تُدندنين طوال الوقت
It's nice that you're happy, but think about how I feel.
من اللّطيف أن تكوني سعيدة، لكن فكّري في مشاعري
Y-You're right.
مـ-معكِ حقّ
You had to be patient and wait the whole time I was studying.
توجّبَ عليكِ أن تصبري وتنتظري طوال فترة دراستي
I'll be more careful.
سأكون أكثر حذراً
You won't be able to go to school with me anymore.
لن تتمكّني من الذهاب إلى المدرسة معي بعد الآن
Doesn't that make you sad?
ألا يُحزنكِ هذا؟
Didn't you say you were excited to go by yourself?
ألم تقولي بأنّكِ متحمّسة للذهاب بمفردكِ؟
No.
لا
You did, though...
...لكنّكِ فعلتِ
Well, it makes me kinda sad.
في الحقيقة، هذا يُحزنني بعض الشيء
You'll be in third grade, huh?
ستكونين في الصفّ الثّالث، صحيح؟
And you'll be in your first year again!
!وأنتِ ستكونين في سنتكِ الأولى من جديد
Yep, that's right.
أجل، هذا صحيح
You know what? I'm just as nervous as I am happy.
أتعلمين؟ أنا متوتّرة بقدر ما أنا سعيدة
I don't know if I'll be able to make friends.
لا أعلم ما إن كنتُ سأتمكّن من تشكيل أصدقاء
A lot of kids from Tokyo go there.
يذهب كثير من الأطفال من طوكيو إلى هناك
I can't help wondering if I'll be able to keep up.
لا يسعني سوى التّفكير فيما إذا كنتُ سأتمكّن من مُجاراتهم
You don't have to worry about that.
ليس عليكِ القلق بشأن ذلك
'Cause you're really cool!
!لأنّكِ رائعة حقّاً
Thanks.
شكراً
Hey! You don't even believe me, do you?
أنتِ! ألا تصدّقينني حتّى؟
Believe it!
!صدّقي ذلك
Okay. I will.
حسناً. سأفعل
We'll both be on our own. Let's do our best.
كلتانا سنكون بمفردنا. لنبذل قصارى جهدنا
'Kay!
!حسناً
Komichi...
...كوميتشي
Got a minute?
هل لي بدقيقة؟
It's done already?
انتهى بهذه السّرعة؟
Not yet.
ليس بعد
This is known as "tacking."
"يُدعى هذا بـ"التثبيت
We use a different fabric to get all the details set before making the real one.
نستخدم نسيجاً مختلفاً لتجهيز كلّ التّفاصيل قبل صنع الحقيقيّ
I didn't know making a uniform was so much work.
لم أكن أعلم أنّ صنع زيّ رسميّ يتطلّب كلّ هذا الجهد
Mom!
!أمّي
The laundry's done!
!انتهى الغسيل
I'll do the cleaning, too!
!سأقوم بالتنظيف أيضاً
Uh, thanks...
...شكراً
Mom, I'll do the dishes!
!أمّي، سوف أجلي الصّحون
Mom, I'm almost done!
!أمّي، شارفتُ على الانتهاء
Mom!
!أمّي
Onee-chan, you're wasting water!
!أونيه-تشان، أنتِ تهدرين الماء
Komichi...
...كوميتشي
Come on over here.
تعالي إلى هنا
And now...
...والآن
It's done.
أصبح جاهزاً
Here, try it on.
هيّا، جرّبيه
O-Okay.
حـ-حسناً
I'll be waiting downstairs.
سأنتظر في الطابق السّفلي
Hey, I like this one.
يُعجبني هذا
Don't you think you're a little too young for that?
ألا تعتقدين بأنّكِ صغيرة زيادة عن اللّزوم على ذلك؟
It's fine!
!لا مشكلة
Onee-chan, you look so cool!
!أونيه-تشان، تبدين رائعة للغاية
Komichi, does it fit okay?
كوميتشي، هل مقاسه مناسب؟
Yeah...
...أجل
Yeah.
أجل
Thank you.
شكراً لكِ
Roubai Academy Middle School Entrance Ceremony
المدرسة الإعداديّة الأكاديميّة روباي مراسم الدّخول
A few things have changed, but it really brings back memories.
تغيّرت بضعة أمور، لكن يعيدني هذا للذكريات
I'm so nervous.
أنا متوتّرة جدّاً
I wonder if she's a new student... Wait...
...أتساءل ما إن كانت تلميذة جديدة... لحظة
Huh?
ماذا؟
Blazers?
سترة؟
Komichi...
...كوميتشي
Is there some other event going on today?
هل هناك حدث آخر يُقام اليوم؟
N-No...
...لـ-لا
Allow me to congratulate you all on your acceptance into this school.
اسمحن لي أن أبارك لكُن جميعاً على قبولكن في هذه المدرسة
As of today, you are all students of Roubai Academy.
اعتباراً من اليوم، جميعكن تلاميذ في أكاديميّة روباي
Komichi!
!كوميتشي
For many years, this school has prepared many excellent students for...
لسنوات عديدة، حضّرت هذه المدرسة الكثير ...من التّلميذات المُتميّزات
Mom!
!أمّي
We're back.
عدنا
Welcome home!
!أهلاً بعودتكما
Onee-chan, how'd it go?
أونيه-تشان، ما الأخبار؟
Sorry, not now.
آسفة، ليس الآن
What's wrong with her?
ما مشكلتها؟
I'm so sorry I didn't confirm what the uniform was first!
أنا آسفة جدّاً لأنّني لم أتحقّق من الزيّ !الرسميّ المطلوب أوّلاً
Well, the students did wear sailor uniforms when you attended here.
كانت التّلميذات هنا ترتدين زيّ بحّارة رسميّاً هنا في أيّامكِ
It's quite understandable.
لذا لستِ مُلامة
Besides, we've known since the interview that Komichi-san dreamed of wearing a sailor uniform.
فضلاً عن ذلك، كنّا نعلم منذ المقابلة بأنّ كوميتشي-سان حلمت بارتداء زيّ بحّارة رسميّ
It's our fault for not informing her at that time.
كانت غلطتنا لأنّنا لم نخبرها في ذلك الوقت
I understand Yuwa-san made it for you?
أفهم من ذلك أنّ يووا-سان من صنعته لكِ؟
Yes! We picked out the fabrics together, and...
...أجل! اخترنا الأقمشة معاً و
I see.
هكذا إذاً
My mother made my school uniform, too.
أمّي من صنعت زيّي المدرسيّ الرّسمي أيضاً
It made me so very happy.
أسعدني ذلك كثيراً
Considering the circumstances,
،نظراً للظروف
the school will permit Komichi-san to wear her sailor uniform.
ستسمح المدرسة لكوميتشي-سان بارتداء زيّ البحّارة الرسميّ الخاص بها
Principal?!
!حضرة المديرة؟
It is an accepted uniform of this school, albeit one from the past.
،إنّه زيّ رسميّ مقبول في هذه المدرسة ولو أنّه من الماضي
We have no reason to forbid it.
لا نملك سبباً لمنعه
But I will leave the final decision to Komichi-san and her family.
لكن سأدع القرار النّهائي لكوميتشي-سان وعائلتها
It'll only be me. That's just...
...سأكون أنا الوحيدة التي ترتديه. هذا
Your congratulatory dinner is ready.
عشاء التّهنئة لكِ جاهز
You get two egg yolks.
حصّتكِ هي قطعتين من صفار البيض
Kao, did you hear what happened?
كاو، هل سمعتِ ما حدث؟
Yep.
أجل
Blazers are cute too, aren't they?
السّترات ظريفة أيضاً، أليس كذلك؟
Ow!
!مؤلم
Wh-What was that for?!
!ما-ما المشكلة؟
So now you hate the sailor uniform Mom made for you?!
هل تكرهين الآن زيّ البحّارة الرسميّ !الّذي صنعته أمّي لكِ؟
I never said that!
!لم أقل ذلك
You're not cool anymore!
!لم تعودي رائعة
Stupid sister!
!أونيه-تشان الغبيّة
I swear, it's not like that!
!أقسم أنّ الأمر ليس كذلك
I don't hate it. I love it.
لا أكرهه. بل أحبّه
But I don't want everyone to think I'm weird.
لكن لا أريد من الجميع أن يعتقدنني غريبة أطوار
'Cause you're really cool!
!لأنّكِ رائعة حقّاً
I want to be seen as cool.
أريد أن يراني الجميع رائعة
And I want to make lots of friends.
وأريد تشكيل الكثير من الأصدقاء
If I'm the only one in a sailor uniform, I know I'll stand out.
إذا كنتُ الوحيدة بزيّ بحّارة مُوحّد، فأنا متأكّدة بأنّني سألفت الأنظار
Maybe that'll be my chance?
ربّما ستكون هذه فرصتي؟
Onee-chan?
أونيه-تشان؟
You're leaving already?
ستغادرين من الآن؟
Thanks.
شكراً
Komichi... Are you sure?
كوميتشي... هل أنتِ متأكّدة؟
Confidence and a smile, right?
الثّقة والابتسامة، صحيح؟
Go get 'em!
!اذهبي وافعليها
Off I go!
!سأغادر
Whoa... I cut it kinda close.
مـ-مهلاً... كدتُ أفشل
Hmm... I'm not sure...
...لستُ متأكّدة
But...
...لكن
I think I've sobered up a little.
أظنّني صحوتُ قليلاً
Okay!
!حسناً
Here I go!
!ها أنا ذي
Cherry blossoms!
!أزهار الكرز
Roubai Academy
أكاديميّة روباي
I think... I got... a little too fired up.
أظنّني... تحمّستُ... زيادة عن اللّزوم
It's so big! It looks like a castle!
!ما أكبرها! كما لو أنّها قلعة
Am I the first one here?
هل أنا أوّل الواصلات إلى هنا؟
New First-Years     Class List
قائمة الصّفوف      السّنة الأولى الجدُد
Class 3
الصفّ 3
Seat Number
رقم المقعد
Name
الاسم
Akebi  Komichi
أكيبي كوميتشي
Usagihara Touko
أوساغيهارا توكو
Ohkuma Minoru
أوكوما مينورو
Kamimoku Neko
كاميموكو نيكو
I've got seat number 1.
رقم مقعدي هو 1
Class 3...
...الصفّ 3
Here it is.
ها هو
Someone's already here?!
!إحداهن هنا بالفعل؟
What if she's really scary?!
!ماذا لو كانت مُخيفة؟
Wow, what a weird outfit!
!يا له من زيّ غريب
I-It's not weird!
!لـ-ليس غريباً
We should try to get along!
!ينبغي أن نحاول الانسجام معاً
Osu!
!أوسو
Why am I trying to fight them?!
!لماذا أحاول مقاتلتهم؟
Um...
...المعذرة
Good morning.
صباح الخير
Good... morning...
...صباح... الخير
Please forget you ever saw that!
!أرجوكِ انسي بأنّكِ رأيتِ ذلك
I mean... you saw me, didn't you?
أعني... رأيتِني، أليس كذلك؟
When I was smelling my own feet on the nail clippers.
عندما شممتُ رائحة قدميّ من قلّامة الأظافر
That's what she was doing?
هذا ما كانت تفعله؟
Sure. I won't tell anyone.
بالتأكيد. لن أخبر أحداً
But... do your feet smell that much?
لكن... هل تفوح رائحة قدميكِ إلى هذه الدّرجة؟
D-Don't question me about it!
!لـ-لا تسأليني عن ذلك
I'm embarrassed enough!
!أنا مُحرَجة بما يكفي
I think I'm curious now, too.
أظنّني أشعر بالفضول الآن أيضاً
Hey!
!أنتِ
I ran here, so I think they might smell a little sweaty.
سارعتُ إلى هنا، لذا أعتقد أنّه تفوح منها رائحة عرق قليلاً
I can see how you'd get into it, though!
I can see how you'd get into it, though!
You're kind of interesting.
أنتِ مثيرة للاهتمام حقّاً
No way! I did it, Kao!
!مستحيل! فعلتُها يا كاو
She called your sister "interesting"!
!"وصفَتْ أختكِ بـ"المثيرة للاهتمام
Hey... Would you mind talking with me a little more?
هل تمانعين أن تتكلّمي معي أكثر قليلاً؟
Oh... So you're going to wear the sailor uniform from now on?
إذاً سترتدين زيّ البحّارة الرسميّ من الآن فصاعداً؟
That's pretty gutsy.
هذا جريء جدّاً
You're Kizaki Erika-san, and you're from T-Tokyo.
أنتِ كيزاكي إيريكا-سان، ومن طـ-طوكيو
Th-That's amazing!
!هـ-هذا رائع
You're taking notes?
أتدوّنين ملاحظات؟
You're very diligent, Akebi-san.
أنتِ مُجتهدة جدّاً يا أكيبي-سان
Y-Your nail clippers are really cute.
قـ-قلّامة أظافركِ ظريفة للغاية
Do you carry them around all the time?
هل تحملينها معكِ طوال الوقت؟
No, this is the first time.
لا، هذه أوّل مرّة
In my room at home, when I get anxious or nervous,
،في غرفتي في المنزل، عندما أتوتّر
I end up clipping my nails.
أقلّم أظافري
This clicking sound just...
...صوت التّقليم هذا
relaxes me somehow.
يهدّئني بطريقة ما
Were you anxious just now?
هل كنتِ متوتّرة قبل قليل؟
Well... with all the firsts I'm experiencing today,
،في الواقع... كلّ ما أجرّبه اليوم هو أوّل مرّة بالنسبة لي
I couldn't sleep last night.
أصابني الأرق في اللّيلة الماضية
I came to school early because I couldn't just sit around any longer,
أتيتُ إلى المدرسة باكراً لأنّني لم أستطع ،الانتظار فترة أطول
but I just kept getting more nervous.
لكن ازددتُ توتّراً وقلقاً فحسب
Is it that funny?
هل هذا طريف؟
No, it's not that.
لا، ليس كذلك
I was just surprised someone as pretty as you would stress like that.
تفاجأتُ فقط من أن تتوتّر فتاة جميلة مثلكِ هكذا
O-Of course I do!
!مـ-من الطبيعي أن أتوتّر
And my looks have nothing to do with it!
!ولا علاقة بمظهري بذلك
Y-Yeah, you're right.
أ-أجل، معكِ حقّ
I was kinda scared, though.
لكن كنتُ خائفة بعض الشيء
I've never really talked to someone my own age before.
لم يسبق أن تكلّمتُ مع شخص في مثل سنّي
I didn't know what I'd do if I didn't think the way everyone else does.
لم أعرف ماذا سأفعل إذا لم يكن تفكيري مطابقاً لتفكير الأخريات
So I'm happy!
!لذلك أنا سعيدة
I felt the same way!
!خالجَني نفس الشّعور
Oh, I guess everyone else will be coming in soon.
أعتقد أنّ الأخريات سيدخلن قريباً
I was just sitting at a random desk.
كنتُ أجلس في مقعد عشوائيّ فحسب
Number 1...
...الرّقم 1
This one's mine.
هذا المقعد لي
The closest spot to greet everyone coming in...
...المكان الأقرب لإلقاء التحيّة على كلّ من يدخل
I'm number 5.
مقعدي هو 5
I think I've calmed down a little.
أظنّني استرخيتُ قليلاً
I'll be okay now.
سأكون بخير الآن
Maybe I can do this, too.
ربّما يمكنني فعلها أيضاً
Good morning!
!صباح الخير